[I wanna be the Just Trap 2 REMAKE]

If you know original context, you probably already know what this type of game is.
But if you don't, then be prepared to face Happil styled bosses.
This game is bossrush and I have no idea why in game they were called as stages.
I put a lot of efforts into this game to make original humanly impossible bosses much more enjoyable.

Here's a list of planned and released bosses:

Stage 1: JR & Justist (I wanna be the GR; I wanna be the Sadist)
Status: [Remade]
Music: [Chikara] by Yoshimi Kudo / 工藤吉三. (https://youtu.be/-TwNjk6TgGY)

Stage 2: Justularity (I wanna be the Popularity)
Status: [Remade]
Music: [Mega Man 5: Boss Battle] by Synthescissor (https://youtu.be/9VyNUyB8paA)
[Mega Man 5: Final Battle] by 化マ (https://nicovideo.jp/watch/sm34410241)

Stage 3: Justrimson (I wanna be the Crimson)
Status: [Remade]
Music: [Red Bee (True Last Boss)] by [Kota Hoshino] (https://youtu.be/9hWh1DOA-ss)

Stage 4: Justination (I wanna be the Destination)
Status: [Remade]
Music: [Black Out Zone] by Jerico's Law. (https://youtu.be/vZyRfXBPGGg)

Stage 5: JUSTAS (I wanna be the TAS)
Status: [Replaced]
New stage 5 boss: Just Out (I wanna make it Breaking Out)

Final boss: Just Trap (I wanna be the Love Trap)
Status: [1/4 done]
Music: [V -conclusion-] by DJ Taka (https://youtu.be/GLS-O2BxSlQ?si=hiQ5JO-j6W5shkyF)

Menu theme music: [Dancing Girl] from [Hyperdimension Neptuinio Re;Birth]
(https://youtu.be/vZyRfXBPGGg)

Music in hub room: [Madness Combat 4 Full Remake] by Lothyde
(https://www.newgrounds.com/audio/listen/907940)

You can find all used songs in YouTube playlist: [https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLWiPX82Y15BxXpTTAMcrCGCz15XxzrEt4]

This remake made by me, Essisten.
Original game made by Just.

Contact me and report any bugs or glitches:

Discord: Essisten (I'm member of I wanna Community server).
X: https://x.com/essisten
VK: https://vk.com/id334913416
Delicious Fruit: https://delicious-fruit.com/profile.php?u=3338.

Help with music:
[AntiColour] for helping me to find the original boss themes.
[FruitlessWasabi] helping with finding a suitable remix for Gravityman.

Help with graphics:
[MisterMike], [Rabbid4240], [Accuracy#1015] for ripping the original Gravityman sprites from the game (sprite-resource).
[Square] for helping me to edit Gravityman's sprite and create a shiny version of the new death screen.
[Leslie] for another beautiful variation of the new death screen with dots.
[DorimecHouse] for remaking the amazing game title sprite!

Testers:
[MyLiE] an incredibly huge amount of feedback, dozens of reported glitches and help with balancing the game. One of the first to beat bosses on Easy difficulty and helped with advices on how to improve them.
[Dzareg] lots of feedback and suggestions. Reported many glitches and tested gamepad compatability. Might be the #1 fan of the game.
[Renko97] tests it every time a new version is released and is one of the first to report errors, which let's me quickly update it. One of the first to beat the bosses on Very Easy difficulty and posted it on YouTube, which helped to promote the game.
[FruitlessWasabi] Gravityman testing and general support during it's development.
[spk] a huge amount of feedback in the early stages of development.

Special thanks to:
[Just] for inspiring me with your unusual projects.
I love the combination of madness and bipolarity, sometimes spiced up with Korean memes. I put you on par with Kamilia and Influka in terms of legend, if not higher.
[Kelvar] is the one who helped me to learn GameMaker when I had to look for tutorials online. My best friend who always helped me. From the very beginning, I wanted to reach and surpass your skill level in game development. I wonder how close I am to this?
[Tasffil] for creating a TAS based on my game. Judging by the number of restarts, it was very difficult for you, wasn’t it? I really hope that the latest version of the project at the latest difficulty will be technically possible.
[Square] circle.
[Game Player Dark] has been streaming old versions of the game since ancient times. I love watching your streams (昔からゲームの古いバージョンをストリーミングしていましたね。 あなたのストリームに来るのが大好きです).
[--Jack/] (--ジャック/) recorded the gameplay of the game with commentary, which helped to promote the game to the Japanese audience. I'm watching you with auto-translator in subtitles (コメント付きでゲームのゲームプレイを撮影し、日本の視聴者にゲームを宣伝するのに役立ちました。 字幕の自動翻訳で見ています).

Also special thanks to every player who reads this and plays this game. It sounds banal and hackneyed, but I remember almost every player who contacted me or have posted a video. Thank you all.